Hello Hello Friends Welcome back to the
stock market. Today we are going to talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance and its staff nurses
fly for August 28th. We have
opened this chart on our chat.
I have opened this chart in my Zerodha account. If
you do not have a demat account, then the
description is below and if you want, you
can
subscribe to us. So
here as you can see, today
such general insurance has
got a positive closing. The
closing is 3055.50. So
in the coming days, we are going to visit here or
we will talk, please
subscribe and definitely subscribe.
And
see here, let's see here, in the coming days,
so
open here. A little volume is being
received here,
due to this,
share it here.
But remember, whether it is RS or
any other indicator, we
cannot rely on the acid, there are a lot of
minerals here, so we must do any of it.
Whenever we do any, then keep it
in mind,
we should do a little here
and here.
So
subscribe, then after that here in
2016 I will
definitely subscribe here again or here here as much as possible, so
open here a
little bit, those who have decided that is, at the moment,
we have to sacrifice a little bit, but therefore
you should find as good a loan as possible, that is,
your restrictive and
from this you will get profit, there you have to
watch the video,
what do you think here, what can happen in the stock in the coming days, do
tell us by commenting, but if you have started subscribing to our channel, then
definitely
subscribe to our channel and if you also want to
start investing in your mutual fund here, it may be so or
we all have our advice, it is
important here, raisins, definitely ask questions above, we will
click on my WhatsApp
number below, if you have
invested in mutual fund from here, then send the link of that,
from there you can definitely go and
start your mutual fund investment like this and understand, so let's go now, we have
made charts, now let's talk about
what to see in stocks tomorrow  Warner's fan is going to be available here, it has
already been opened,
important support is just
registration, all the people do not need to mark Bloody Mary, let
us talk directly about the area which is most shy at the closing time,
note
it means
school,
so here you have to
wait on any one of the two sides,
then definitely
subscribe to the channel,
share and
subscribe, you
can also subscribe to intraday stocks, do
subscribe to
[sangeet],
so here I will tell you, here
director Mukesh Bhatt is of 3239, after that of
3034, here hatred against director is of
2065, after that from 8, here I will
definitely tell you the two supports in two parts, keeping that in consideration,
my yesterday's loose here, now I am
clicking on today's closing basis in my bin stock, then in my office
stock, you will definitely have a negative effort that
we will get to see NSS
closing in PDS range at the rate of 32318,
what do you think here in the stock  Please do let
us know what your day might be by commenting.
If you like my device,
please like and share our video
and don't forget to subscribe to our channel.
Thank you.